TSHILIDZI RAMBUDA

Web Developer / Designer

Energetic Front-End Developer with experience and passion for working with programming languages like php, JavaScript, html, react.js and CSS. passionate about programming, driving brand loyalty, and increasing productivity. Exposed to deadline-intensive settings as a result gained the ability to work under pressure.

EDUCATION

Phomolong Secondary School

2010 - 2014

Majored in Physical Sciences (Matric)

Ekurhuleni West College

2016 - 2018

Majored in Information Technology (Certificate)

Chongqing Polytechnic College

2019 - 2020

Majored in Computer Science and Data Analysis (International Certificate)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Trip.com

Internet (Intern)

2019 - 2020

Key roles:

- Data analysis
- Client and Business interactions
- Internal Data system Operations

ECAT Online Web developer

2021 - Currently

Key roles:

- Web Development and design, SEO, Online Marketing Research and Development.
- Website updates and testing
- Working with XML and XSL for data updates
- Image editing and graphic design.
- Building responsive and user-friendly websites
- Interpreting client specifications to designs and development.

SKILLS

HTML5 and CSS3

- Using html5 and Css3 to build PWA web applications
- Build modern and responsive websites
- SASS (CSS)

JavaScript

- Client-side application development
- React.js (intermediate)
- Node.js(intermediate)
- Browser compatibility

CONTACT ME

Email: rambudatshilidzi1@gmail.com

Call: 0670295684

Linked In: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tshilidzi-rambuda-7796b6168/